ANTOINE NEIDECKER

PRODUCT MANAGER

+33 6 95 14 96 33 antoine.neidecker@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am driven with a passion for solving difficult problems. Four times founder, I want to work in an established company with like-minded individuals. I have a passion for collaborating in fast-paced environments. I am a physicist / computer scientist by education with a track record of delivering difficult technical problems. I have 7 years of experience leading product development with teams ranging from 4 to 8 people. Raised over \$1M in last startup and was featured on international TV show.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Leadership Experience Senior Developer Agile Development Public Speaking Frontend, Backend Machine Learning Python, Swift, JS Google Cloud

EDUCATION

McGill University 2014 - 2019

Bachelor of Science in Physics and Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

Co-Founder | CTO

October 2020- October 2022

Train Fitness

Led the development of a B2C SaaS with over 15,000 weekly active users. Train Fitness enables users to track their workouts automatically using motion detection Al. Pitched on Canadian TV show Dragon's Den. Raised over \$1M and managed 8 employees.

- Led quarterly OKRs (Objective and Key Results) for Frontend, Backend features, Al, Data targets, growth and design.
- Leveraged Data Analytics to identify user behavior and validate / disprove hypothesis
- Managed and developed data pipeline and deep neural network core AI (Patent pending).
- Led backend team in 4 week sprints to develop Serverless architecture and Firebase with associated extensions.
- Developed frontend features. Notable frontend projects: Al running on edge, Authentication, Hardware limitations.

Founder I CTO

October 2019 - September 2020

KixAl

Al based recommender system for shoes.

- Developed Web Scraper (Python) and iPhone App (Swift)
- Developed Recommender system based on collaborative filtering and content based methods

Co-Founder | Product Lead

October 2016 - June 2017

Mtg.ai

Software which transcribes and sumarizes business meetings.

• Managed frontend and ML (NLP) development using Agile Methodology (Jira)

Co-Founder | CEO

September 2014 - October 2016

Fractal

Knowledge management tool based on innovative user interface.

- Conceived the product, features, and interface
- Pitched the product, led a team of 8 and planned the team's weekly sprints and won prizes.